<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>  on Sahil Sharma</title>
    <link>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in   on Sahil Sharma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project-1: Covid-19 Analysis</title>
      <link>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: The disease COVID-19, which is brought on by the coronavirus SARS-CoV-2, which first surfaced in 2019, is well known to all. COVID-19 is severe and had caused the deaths of millions of people in the world, left millions of families to strive, and plunged the economy of several countries. Objective: In this project, my whole aim was to present the data visually to find out the answers to the following questions: How many cases were repored in the different countries?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project-2: Rotten Tomatoes Web Scrapper</title>
      <link>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: We all data enthusiasts know the one of the famous saying that Data is the new Oil. But there comes a big question in my mind every time I come across with it that:
How would you get this oil? How would you mine it? How much amount do we need to pay? Is there any special machinary used to extract this data? Objective: With all these questions in my mind, I came up with an idea to build a web scrapper to scrape the reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project-3: American Bank Analysis</title>
      <link>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: The banking industry heavily relies on big data analytics. Where real-time analysis of the data helps banks to identify fraudulent transactions, and big data analysis to identify customer spending behavior and loan defaulters.
In this project I worked on a sample of the banking data, which had information about the customers of the American Bank.
Objective: The aim of this project was to answer the question asked by the bank manager and other stakeholders, such as:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Sahil, a Computer Engineering Graduate by qualification but a Data Analyst by blood.
Presently, I&amp;rsquo;m working in TCS as a developer, where my role is to analyse the events coming from the different network elements and filter them using the SQL queries.
Now coming to my passion (which is Data Analytics off course 😄). Well, we all know that data is everywhere, but how to make use of that raw, untidy data for making a strategic move in the organization is kind of big deal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anonhan.github.io/Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description> Follow me on these social media platforms. Platform URL GitHub: https://www.github.com/anonHan LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sahilthedataanalyst Email: sahiltheanalyst@gmail.com Contact: +91 8825083491 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
